Finding Aid for the Photograph Album Collection LSC.0094
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Photograph album of Rio de Janeiro, 1960s; no.321
  See the OAC record for this photograph album: Photograph album of Rio de Janeiro
- Photograph album of views of the Ferrocarril Central from Callao to Chicla, Peru, 1882-1889; no.322
- Venezuelan vistas: Spanish American life, and some notes on a year in Caracas, the capital city of Venezuela, 1890; no.323
- Photograph album of Montevideo, 1892; no.324
  See the OAC record for this photograph album: Photograph album of Montevideo
- Recuerdos del Perú, 1863-1871; no.325
  See the OAC record for this photograph album: Recuerdos del Perú
- Photograph album of "Green Gates," Coldwater Canyon, Beverly Hills, California, 1925-1932; no.326
  See the OAC record for this photograph album: Photograph album of "Green Gates," Coldwater Canyon, Beverly Hills, Calif.
- Facsimile of the album presented to Lady Caperton by the Directorate of the Port of Montevideo, 1918; no.327
  See the OAC record for this photograph album: Fac=simil of the album presented to Lady Caperton by the Directorate of the Port of Montevideo
- Vistas de Montevideo, 1919; no.328
  See the OAC record for this photograph album: Vistas de Montevideo 1919
- Photographs referred to in Engineer's Report, 1902-1903; no.329
  See the OAC record for this photograph album: Photographs referred to in Engineer's Report
- Souvenir of Lude. Dundee, 1871; no.330; (1 vol., 32 × 39 cm. Photograph album with approximately 30 [19 × 24 cm.] mounted photographs)
  Scope and Contents
- Views of Scotland, 1880s; (1 vol., 32 × 43 cm. Photograph album with various size albumen prints)
  See the OAC record for this photograph album: Photograph album of views of Scotland